<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string formatted="false" name="app_label">BI Plugin - Classic</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="settings_activity_name">Battery Indicator Pro - Plugin Settings</string>

  <string formatted="false" name="pref_hint">Hint: Press MENU for help.</string>

  <string formatted="false" name="pref_cat_color">Icon Color</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_cat_color_help">
    In order to keep the binary package for Battery Indicator
    reasonably small, there are some limitations for the colors.  At
    the time of writing, you can have a red icon as high as 30%, an
    amber icon as high as 50%, and a green icon as low as 20%.  I
    think these are reasonable compromises that should work for 99% of
    users.\n

    \nTo give you maximum control, the colors can be turned on or off
    independently.  This means that you can have as much as a
    four-tiered color scheme, where the icon is green when it is very
    full, then grayscale, then amber, then red.  Of course, most
    people probably have the amber and green thresholds set to the
    same value, so that the icon is never grayscale.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_color_preview">Color Preview</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_color_preview_help">
    The color preview will hopefully make it really easy to visualize
    what effect your color settings will have.\n

    \nThis doesn\'t exist in 10% mode, because it just wouldn\'t make
    sense.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red">Use Red Icon</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_summary">Use red icon when charge is low?</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_help">
    Whether or not to use a red icon below the specified threshold.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_thresh">Red Threshold</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_thresh_summary">Red icon below what charge percentage:</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_thresh_summary10">Red icon at or below what charge percentage:</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_red_thresh_help">Specifies the charge level which
    the icon should turn red below (or <i>at</i>, in 10% Mode).\n

    \nThe options for the red threshold include all the values (in
    multiples of 5) for which there are red icons available.\n

    \nIn 10% Mode, things work slightly differently but should be
    self-explanatory.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber">Use Amber Icon</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_summary">Use amber icon when charge is medium?</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_help">
    Whether or not to use an amber icon below the specified threshold.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_thresh">Amber Threshold</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_thresh_summary">Amber icon below what charge percentage:</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_thresh_summary10">Amber icon at or below what charge percentage:</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_amber_thresh_help">Specifies the charge level
    which the icon should turn amber below (or <i>at</i>, in 10%
    Mode).\n

    \nThe options for the amber threshold include all the values (in
    multiples of 5) for which there are amber icons available,
    starting 5 percentage points above the red threshold (if there is
    one).  For example, if you have the red threshold set to 15, then
    your lowest option here will be 20.\n

    \nIn 10% Mode, things work slightly differently but should be
    self-explanatory.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green">Use Green Icon</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green_summary">Use green icon when charge is high?</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green_help">
    Whether or not to use a green icon at or above the specified threshold.
  </string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green_thresh">Green Threshold</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green_thresh_summary">Green icon at or above what charge percentage:</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_green_thresh_help">Specifies the charge level
    which the icon should be green at or above.\n

    \nThe options for the green threshold include all the values (in
    multiples of 5) for which there are green icons available,
    starting at the highest active threshold you have set for red or
    amber.  For example, if you have the amber threshold set to 40,
    then your lowest option here will be 40.\n

    \nIn 10% Mode, things work slightly differently but should be
    self-explanatory.
  </string>

  <string formatted="false" name="pref_ten_percent_mode">10% Mode</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_ten_percent_mode_summary">Read the help first!</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="pref_ten_percent_mode_help"><b>Note:</b>
    Checking or unchecking this will reset your icon color settings!\n

    \nThis setting cleans up the Icon Color settings to make more
    sense on devices that only show their charge level in 10%
    increments. Most Motorola devices need this, especially the Droid
    line.
  </string>

  <string formatted="false" name="confirm_ten_percent_enable">Really enable 10% Mode?</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="confirm_ten_percent_disable">Really disable 10% Mode?</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="confirm_ten_percent_hint">
    Warning: Changing this setting (both enabling and disabling it)
    will reset your color settings.\n

    \nIf your phone really only shows you 10% increments, you should
    turn this on when you first get the plugin, and then leave it
    alone.  Otherwise you should always leave this off.
  </string>

  <string formatted="false" name="currently_using">Currently using</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="currently_set_to">"Currently set to: "</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="currently_disabled">Currently Disabled</string>

  <string formatted="false" name="yes">Yes</string>
  <string formatted="false" name="cancel">Cancel</string>

  <string formatted="false" name="menu_help">Help</string>
</resources>
